{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IENhbGwgb2YgRHV0eSB0aXRsZSByZWxlYXNlZD8=","correct_answer":"T2N0b2JlciAyOXRoLCAyMDAz","incorrect_answers":["RGVjZW1iZXIgMXN0LCAyMDAz","Tm92ZW1iZXIgMTR0aCwgMjAwMg==","SnVseSAxOHRoLCAyMDA0"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggd2FzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBvZiBBbGZyZWQgSGl0Y2hjb2NrJ3MgbW92aWVzIHRvIGJlIGZpbG1lZCBpbiBjb2xvdXI\/","correct_answer":"Um9wZQ==","incorrect_answers":["UHN5Y2hv","VmVydGlnbw==","UmViZWNjYQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"T24gd2hpY2ggQmVhdGxlcyBhbGJ1bSB3b3VsZCB5b3UgZmluZCB0aGUgc29uZyAnRWxlYW5vciBSaWdieSc\/","correct_answer":"UmV2b2x2ZXI=","incorrect_answers":["SGVscCE=","UnViYmVyIFNvdWw=","QWJiZXkgUm9hZA=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogTWF0aGVtYXRpY3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgYXBwcm94aW1hdGUgdmFsdWUgb2YgbWF0aGVtYXRpY2FsIGNvbnN0YW50IGU\/","correct_answer":"Mi43Mg==","incorrect_answers":["My4xNA==","MS42Mg==","MS40MQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGxhc3QgQXBoZXggVHdpbiBhbGJ1bSByZWxlYXNlZCBiZWZvcmUgaGlzIGRlY2FkZS1sb25nIGhpYXR1cz8=","correct_answer":"RHJ1a3Fz","incorrect_answers":["V2luZG93bGlja2Vy","U3lybw==","Q29sbGVjdGVkIEFtYmllbnQgV29ya3MgODUtOTI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gdGhlIFN1cGVyIE1hcmlvIEJyb3MuIFNlcmllcywgd2hhdCBpcyBZb3NoaSdzIHNjaWVudGlmaWMgbmFtZT8=","correct_answer":"VC4gWW9zaGlzYXVyIE11bmNoYWtvb3Bhcw==","incorrect_answers":["WW9zaGk=","VC4gWW9zaGlzb3RvcCBNdW5jaGFrb29wYXM=","WW9zc3k="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugc29uZ3Mgd2FzIHJlbGVhc2VkIGluIDE5OTY\/","correct_answer":"VGhlIFNtYXNoaW5nIFB1bXBraW5zIC0gIjE5Nzki","incorrect_answers":["UHJpbmNlIC0gIjE5OTki","SmFtZXMgQmx1bnQgLSAiMTk3MyI=","RGF2aWQgQm93aWUgLSAiMTk4NCI="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyBSb24gV2Vhc2xleSdzIG1pZGRsZSBuYW1lPw==","correct_answer":"QmlsaXVz","incorrect_answers":["QXJ0aHVy","Sm9obg==","RG9taW5pYw=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZSAmIE5hdHVyZQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBjb21tb24gbmFtZSBpcyBnaXZlbiB0byB0aGUgbWVkaWFsIGNvbmRpdGlvbiwgdGliaWFsIHN0cmVzcyBzeW5kcm9tZSAoTVRTUyk\/","correct_answer":"U2hpbiBTcGxpbnRz","incorrect_answers":["VGVubmlzIEVsYm93","Q2FycGFsIFR1bm5lbA==","SG91c2VtYWlkJ3MgS25lZQ=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHdvcmxkJ3MgZmlyc3QgdmlkZW8gZ2FtZT8=","correct_answer":"VGVubmlzIGZvciBUd28=","incorrect_answers":["U3BhY2V3YXIh","UG9uZw==","U3BhY2UgVHJhdmVs"]},{"category":"R2VvZ3JhcGh5","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgcHJvdmluY2UgaW4gQ2hpbmE\/","correct_answer":"WWFuZ3R6ZQ==","incorrect_answers":["RnVqaWFu","U2ljaHVhbg==","R3Vhbmdkb25n"]},{"category":"UG9saXRpY3M=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggTmF0aXZlIEFtZXJpY2FuIHRyaWJlL25hdGlvbiByZXF1aXJlcyBhdCBsZWFzdCBvbmUgaGFsZiBibG9vZCBxdWFudHVtIChlcXVpdmFsZW50IHRvIG9uZSBwYXJlbnQpIHRvIGJlIGVsaWdpYmxlIGZvciBtZW1iZXJzaGlwPw==","correct_answer":"WW9tYmEgU2hvc2hvbmUgVHJpYmU=","incorrect_answers":["U3RhbmRpbmcgUm9jayBTaW91eCBUcmliZQ==","S2lvd2EgVHJpYmUgb2YgT2tsYWhvbWE=","UGF3bmVlIE5hdGlvbiBvZiBPa2xhaG9tYQ=="]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"TGlzdCB0aGUgZm9sbG93aW5nIElyYW5pYyBlbXBpcmVzIGluIGNocm9ub2xvZ2ljYWwgb3JkZXI6","correct_answer":"TWVkaWFuLCBBY2hhZW1lbmlkLCBQYXJ0aGlhbiwgU2Fzc2FuaWQ=","incorrect_answers":["TWVkaWFuLCBBY2hhZW1lbmlkLCBTYXNzYW5pZCwgUGFydGhpYW4=","QWNoYWVtZW5pZCwgTWVkaWFuLCBQYXJ0aGlhbiwgU2Fzc2FuaWQ=","QWNoYWVtZW5pZCwgTWVkaWFuLCBTYXNzYW5pZCwgUGFydGhpYW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gIlNvbmljIHRoZSBIZWRnZWhvZyAyIiBmb3IgdGhlIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcywgd2hhdCBkbyB5b3UgaW5wdXQgaW4gdGhlIHNvdW5kIHRlc3Qgc2NyZWVuIHRvIGFjY2VzcyB0aGUgc2VjcmV0IGxldmVsIHNlbGVjdD8=","correct_answer":"VGhlIExlYWQgUHJvZ3JhbW1lcidzIGJpcnRoZGF5","incorrect_answers":["VGhlIGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIg==","VGhlIGRhdGUgU29uaWMgVGVhbSB3YXMgZm91bmRlZA==","VGhlIGZpcnN0IHJlbGVhc2UgZGF0ZSBvZiAiU29uaWMgdGhlIEhlZGdlaG9nIDIi"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"SW4gdGhlIEFuaW1hbCBDcm9zc2luZyBzZXJpZXMsIHdoaWNoIGZsb3dlciBpcyBlcnJvbmVvdXNseSBjYWxsZWQgdGhlICJKYWNvYidzIExhZGRlciI\/","correct_answer":"TGlseSBvZiB0aGUgVmFsbGV5","incorrect_answers":["SHlkcmFuZ2Vh","SGFyZWJlbGw=","WWFycm93"]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogRmlsbQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgYXNzYXNzaW4gaW4gdGhlIGZpcnN0ICJIZWxsYm95IiBtb3ZpZT8=","correct_answer":"S2FybCBSdXByZWNodCBLcm9lbmVu","incorrect_answers":["S2xhdXMgV2VybmVyIHZvbiBLcnVwdA==","R3JpZ29yaSBFZmltb3ZpY2ggUmFzcHV0aW4=","SWxzYSBIYXVwc3RlaW4="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiB0aGVtZSBzb25nIG9mICJTb25pYyBBZHZlbnR1cmUgMiI\/","correct_answer":"TGl2ZSBhbmQgTGVhcm4=","incorrect_answers":["T3BlbiBZb3VyIEhlYXJ0","Q2FuIFlvdSBGZWVsIHRoZSBTdW5zaGluZT8=","SGlzIFdvcmxk"]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggZmlsbSBzdGFyIGhhcyBoaXMgc3RhdHVlIGluIExlaWNlc3RlciBTcXVhcmU\/","correct_answer":"Q2hhcmxpZSBDaGFwbGlu","incorrect_answers":["UGF1bCBOZXdtYW4=","Um93YW4gQXRraW5zb24g","QWxmcmVkIEhpdGNoY29jaw=="]},{"category":"U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"VGhlIGludGVybmV0IGRvbWFpbiAuZm0gaXMgdGhlIGNvdW50cnktY29kZSB0b3AtbGV2ZWwgZG9tYWluIGZvciB3aGljaCBQYWNpZmljIE9jZWFuIGlzbGFuZCBuYXRpb24\/","correct_answer":"TWljcm9uZXNpYQ==","incorrect_answers":["RmlqaQ==","VHV2YWx1","TWFyc2hhbGwgSXNsYW5kcw=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggZ2FtZSB3YXMgZXhjbHVzaXZlIHRvIERyZWFtY2FzdD8=","correct_answer":"UGVuIFBlbiBUcmlJY2Vsb24=","incorrect_answers":["U3lsdmVzdGVyICYgVHdlZXR5IGluIENhZ2V5IENhcGVycw==","UGVyZmVjdCBEYXJr","VGV0cmlzcGhlcmU="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgTk9UIGEgc29uZyBmZWF0dXJlZCBvbiB0aGUgTG9ja2phdyBFUCByZWxlYXNlZCBpbiAyMDEzIGJ5IEZsdW1lICYgQ2hldCBGYWtlcj8=","correct_answer":"TGVmdCBBbG9uZQ==","incorrect_answers":["V2hhdCBBYm91dCBVcw==","VGhpcyBTb25nIElzIE5vdCBBYm91dCBBIEdpcmw=","RHJvcCBUaGUgR2FtZQ=="]},{"category":"R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hpY2ggbXVzaWNpYW4gaGFzIGNvbGxhYm9yYXRlZCB3aXRoIEFtZXJpY2FuIHByb2R1Y2VyIFBvcnRlciBSb2JpbnNvbiBhbmQgcmVsZWFzZWQgdGhlIDIwMTYgc29uZyAiU2hlbHRlciI\/","correct_answer":"TWFkZW9u","incorrect_answers":["TWF0IFpv","ZGVhZG1hdTU=","WmVkZA=="]},{"category":"RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogVmlkZW8gR2FtZXM=","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBkZXZpY2UgYWxsb3dzIFRyYWNlciB0byBtYW5pcHVsYXRlIGhlciBvd24gdGltZSBpbiB0aGUgZ2FtZSAiT3ZlcndhdGNoIj8=","correct_answer":"Q2hyb25hbCBBY2NlbGVyYXRvcg==","incorrect_answers":["Qi5MLkkuTi5L","U3BhY2lhbCBEaXNwbGFjZW1lbnQgTWFuaXB1bGF0b3I=","VE1EIChUaW1lIE1hbmlwdWxhdGlvbiBEZXZpY2Up"]},{"category":"QW5pbWFscw==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIG9mIHRoZSBCdWRnZXJpZ2FyPw==","correct_answer":"TWVsb3BzaXR0YWN1cyB1bmR1bGF0dXM=","incorrect_answers":["TnltcGhpY3VzIGhvbGxhbmRpY3Vz","UHlycmh1cmEgbW9saW5hZQ==","QXJhIG1hY2Fv"]},{"category":"SGlzdG9yeQ==","type":"bXVsdGlwbGU=","difficulty":"aGFyZA==","question":"V2hlbiB3YXMgQWRvbGYgSGl0bGVyIGFwcG9pbnRlZCBhcyBDaGFuY2VsbG9yIG9mIEdlcm1hbnk\/","correct_answer":"SmFudWFyeSAzMHRoLCAxOTMz","incorrect_answers":["U2VwdGVtYmVyIDFzdCwgMTkzOQ==","RmVicnVhcnkgMjd0aCwgMTkzMw==","T2N0b2JlciA2dGgsIDE5Mzk="]}]}